Register of the Fred M. Hechinger Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Speeches and Writings, 1947-1990.; See also Newspaper Columns File, Oversize File, and Scrapbooks
  - "Should Teachers Be Judged by Performance?" Saturday Review World, 1974 May 4. (Folder 32: 6)
  - "The Case Against Preferential Racial Quotas: Justice Douglas's Dissent in the DeFunis Case," Saturday Review World, 1974 July 27. (Folder 32: 7)
  - "Postcript: The Unfinished Promise," chapter of an unidentified book?, 1974 August 9. (Folder 32: 8)
    Typescript and galley
  - "The Case for Educare and the Open University," Saturday Review World, 1974 August 24. (Folder 32: 9)
  - "Whatever Became of Sin?" Saturday Review World, 1974 September 21. (Folder 32: 10)
  - "Lawrence Cremin: Looking Toward the Heights," Saturday Review World, 1974 October 19. (Folder 32: 11)
  - "An Academic Counter-Revolution," Saturday Review World, 1974 November 16. (Folder 32: 12)
  - "Education," Year Book, Macmillan Educational Corporation, 1975. (Folder 32: 13)
    Galley, letter from Deborah Gale, and related materials
  - Growing up in America (with Grace Hechinger), 1975
    - General (Folder 32: 14)
    - Correspondence. (Folder 32: 15-17)
      Includes permission requests
    - Typescript and galley. (Box 33-34)
      Includes related materials
    - Galley (Box-folder 35: 1-3)
    - Galley (Box-folder 36: 1)
    - Printed copy (Folder 36: 2)
    - Reviews and comments. (Folder 36: 3-5)
      Includes other materials
  - "An Experiment with Tradition," Saturday Review, 1975 January 11. (Box-folder 37: 1)
  - "American Higher Education,", 1975 February 15. (Folder 37: 2)
  - "Combating Lingui-Chauvinism: A Biracial, Bilingual Experiment in Ohio," Saturday Review, 1975 March 8. (Folder 37: 3)
  - Paper on the role of education in achieving America's egalitarian ideals, 1975 March 28. (Folder 37: 4)
  - "Due Process for the Unruly Student," Saturday Review, 1975 April 5. (Folder 37: 5)
  - "The All-New 'Law and Order' Classroom," Saturday Review, 1975 May 3. (Folder 37: 6)
    Typescript, galley, and printed copy
  - Article on mathematics, 1975 May 4. (Folder 37: 7)
  - "Loss of Tenure: Return of a Nightmare," Saturday Review, 1975 May 31. (Folder 37: 8)
  - "Morality in Education,", 1975 August 26. (Folder 37: 9)
  - "The Ebb and Flow of Student Rebellion," Saturday Review, 1975 September 6. (Folder 37: 10)
  - "Lifelong Learning: The Back-to-School Boom," and "Education's 'New Majority'," Saturday Review, 1975 September 20. (Folder 37: 11)
    Printed copy and Hungarian translation
  - "Mission for the Third Century," bicentennial address, Curriculum Research and Development Center, University of Rhode Island, Rhode Island, 1975 October 30-November 1. (Folder 37: 12)
    Typescript and letters from Lorraine H. Huckel and H. Stanley Wills
  - "Education: To Say that Education's Ethics Compare Favorably Is not Sufficient Reason to Give It a Passing Grade," Saturday Review, 1975 November 1. (Folder 37: 13)
  - "There's No Way to 'Deliver' Education,", 1975 December? (Folder 37: 14)
    Galley and letter from Jban L. Stableski
  - "A Revolt Against Rank and Birth," Saturday Review, 1975 December 13. (Folder 37: 15)
  - Comments regarding Irv Rosenthal, 1976? (Folder 37: 16)
  - "The World Is a Classroom," review of Lawrence A. Cremin, Public Education, Saturday Review, 1976. (Folder 37: 17)
  - Address, First Annual Distinguished Faculty Awards Banquet, Hershey, Pennsylvania, 1976 February 10. (Folder 37: 18)
    Printed copy and letter from John C. Pittenger
  - "American Character: Its Mind and Spirit," Bicentennial Lecture Series, Temple Emanu-El Spring Program, New York, 1976 March 7. (Folder 37: 19)
    Typescript and related materials
  - "Murder in Academe: The Demise of Education," Saturday Review, 1976 March 20. (Folder 37: 20)
  - "The Audio-Tutorial Approach to Learning," Change, 1976 May? (Folder 37: 21)
    Printed copy and letter
  - "The Unfinished Promise" (with Grace Hechinger), Education Digest, 1976 May. (Folder 37: 22)
  - "Waxworks History," Saturday Review, 1976 May 29. (Folder 37: 23)
  - "Sheepskins in Mothballs," Saturday Review, 1976 August 7. (Folder 37: 24)
  - "The Demise of Education," The Education Digest, 1976 September. (Folder 37: 25)
  - Self-Doubt in American Higher Education," Phi Delta Kappan, 1976 September. (Folder 37: 26)
  - "Education in Trouble: The Demise of Education," Current, 1976 October. (Folder 37: 27)
  - "Career Education,", 1976 October 25. (Box-folder 38: 1)
  - "The Public Perception of Education," speech, College Entrance Examination Board 75th Anniversary Meeting, 1976 October 25. (Folder 38: 2)
    Galley, printed copy and excerpts, correspondence with David Coleman, and related materials
  - "Make the Most of the Crucial Learning Years" (with Grace Hechinger), Parents' Magazine and Better Homemaking, 1976 December. (Folder 38: 3)
    Printed copy and letters from Genevieve Millet Landau
  - "Education," World Book Year Book, Field Enterprises Educational Corporation, 1977. (Folder 38: 4)
    Galley and correspondence with Paul C. Tullier
  - "Upending Segregation," review of Richard Kluger, Simple Justice: The History of Brown V. Board of Education and Black America's Struggle for Equality, Saturday Review, 1977. (Folder 38: 5)
  - "Basics? Yes, But Why Move Backwards?", 1977 February? (Folder 38: 6)
    Galley, letters from the editors of Teacher, and other materials, including printed copy of "The Basic No-Frills Box," undated
  - "An Interview with the President" [Robert E. Marshak], City College, City College Alumni, 1977 February. (Folder 38: 7)
  - "Reappraising the Open Classroom," Saturday Review, 1977 March 19. (Folder 38: 8)
  - "Restoring Public Confidence in the Schools," address, National School Boards Association, Texas, 1977 March 26. (Folder 38: 9)
    Galley, printed copy, Houston Post, letter from Don E. Blom, and related materials
  - Speech on measurement, 1977 April 7. (Folder 38: 10)
    Notes
  - Martin Buskin Memorial Lecture, sponsored by the Education Writers Association, Washington, D.C., 1977 April 22. (Folder 38: 11)
  - "Schools Without Schools," Saturday Review, 1977 April 30 and Education Digest, 1977 October. (Folder 38: 12)
  - "On with the Show," Change, 1977 June. (Folder 38: 13)
  - "The American Culture as Educator," speech, Michigan Chief State School Officers 1977 Summer Institute, 1977 July 29. (Folder 38: 14)
    Galley. Includes printed copy, Beyond The School: What Else Educates?
  - Article on education, Today's Education, 1977 August 1. (Folder 38: 15)
    Galley, letter from Walter A. Graves, and other materials
  - "Education," World Book Year Book, Field Enterprises Educational Corporation, 1978. (Folder 38: 16)
    Galley and letters from Paul C. Tullier
  - "The Back-to-the-Basics Impact," Today's Education, 1978 February-March. (Folder 38: 17)
  - Speech, San Francisco, California, 1978 February 3. (Folder 38: 18)
  - "Retreat from Anarchy," Saturday Review, 1978 April 1. (Folder 38: 19)
  - Keynote address, National Invitational Conference on Regionalism in American Post Secondary Education, sponsored by the Pennsylvania State University, Washington, D.C., 1978 June 8-9. (Folder 38: 20)
    Typescript, letters from S. V. Martorana and Lawrence A. Nespoli, and other materials
  - "Political Issues in Education: Reflections and Directions," speech, Chief State School Officers 1978 Summer Institute, South Padre Island, Texas, 1978 July 31-August 5. (Folder 38: 21)
    Typescript, printed copy, correspondence, and related materials
  - "Searching for the Ideal College Curriculum: Does Harvard Have the Answer?" Today's Education, 1978 November-December. (Folder 38: 22)
  - "The Corporation in the Classroom," Education Digest, 1978 December. (Folder 38: 23)
  - "Education," World Book Year Book, World Book-Childcraft International, 1979. (Folder 38: 24)
    Galley fragment and letter from Paul C. Tullier
  - "About Education: Program Expands World Studies,", 1979 June 26. (Folder 38: 25)
  - "The 80'S: A Prospective Look," speech? 10th Annual Summer Institute, Jeffersonville, Vermont, 1979 July 25-August 2. (Folder 38: 26)
  - Interview with Owen Kiernan, National Association of Secondary School Principals, 1979 September 15. (Box-folder 39: 1)
    Typescript transcript and letters from Thomas F. Koerner and Owen B. Kiernan
  - "A Long Tug-of-War" (with Grace Hechinger), The Wilson Quarterly, 1979 Autumn. (Folder 39: 2)
  - "Education," World Book Year Book, World Book-Childcraft International, 1980. (Folder 39: 3)
    Galley, letters from Paul C. Tullier, and related materials
  - Introduction to Childhood, Youth and Society, 1980. (Folder 39: 4)
    Galley and letter from Christine Bent
  - "The Flap Over 'Life Experience' Credits," Prime Time, 1980 January. (Folder 39: 5)
  - Interview of Clifford Wharton, American Illustrated, International Communication Agency, 1980 October-November? (Folder 39: 6)
    Typescript transcript and correspondence
  - "Education,", 1980 November 11? (Folder 39: 7)
  - "Making Less Become Better," Educational Record, 1980 Winter. (Folder 39: 8)
  - Comments on Michael R. Kelley, Television: Teacher in Our Midst, 1981. (Folder 39: 9)
    Typescript, letter from Dianne Littwin, and related materials
  - "Education," World Book Year Book, World-Book-Childcraft International, 1981. (Folder 39: 10)
    Galley, correspondence with Paul C. Tullier, and related materials
  - "Education Agenda for the 1980s," Fastback 161, Diamond Jubilee Series, Phi Delta Kappa Educational Foundation, 1981. (Folder 39: 11)
  - "Education: The Changing Role of Testing," Americana Annual/The Year Book 1981 (other title, "Education: The Current Role of Testing"), Grolier (Folder 39: 12)
    Typescript, galley, and agreement
  - Foreword to James M. Lipham, Effective Principal, Effective School, 1981. (Folder 39: 13)
    Typescript, galley, printed copy, correspondence with Scott D. Thomson, and related materials
  - Higher Education: Challenges and Opportunities, discussion (with E. K. Fretwell and Paul Simon) on the shape of higher education in the coming decade, National Public Radio, Washington, D.C., 1981
    - Galley. (Folder 39: 14-17)
      Includes notes and related materials
    - Galley (Box-folder 40: 1-2)
  - Higher Learning in the Nation's Service (with Ernest L. Boyer), 1981. (Folder 40: 3)
    Printed copy, review, and correspondence
  - "Private Schools," Americana Annual/Encyclopedia Year Book, 1981. (Folder 40: 4)
    Typescript, galley, and letter from James E. Churchill, Jr.
  - "The Search for Common Ground," commencement speech, State University of New York at New Paltz, New York, 1981 May 17
    - Correspondence. (Folder 40: 5)
      Includes comments
    - Typescript (Folder 40: 6)
    - Printed excerpts, Times Herald Record, 1981 May 18 (Folder 40: 7)
  - "About Education: The Long Road to Teacher of the Year,", 1981 September 15. (Folder 40: 8)
  - Restoring Confidence in Public Education (with Grace Hechinger), 1981 November. (Folder 40: 9)
    Printed copy. Includes typescript speech, Fourth Annual Rudolph Fobert Memorial Lecture, sponsored by Education Collaborative for Greater Boston (EDCO), Boston, Massachusetts, 1982 May 27, and letters from John H. Green
  - "The Effect of Declining Literacy on a Free Press," speech, Can We Teach Our Children to Read? conference, sponsored by the Reading Forum Foundation, City University Graduate Center, New York City, New York, 1981 November 11. (Folder 40: 10)
    Typescript and letters from Sandra Priest Rose
  - "Education," World Book Year Book, World Book – Childcraft International, 1982. (Folder 40: 11)
    Galley and letters from Sara Dreyfus, Paul C. Tullier, and Wayne Wille
  - "Blackburn College," America Illustrated, 1982 August? (Folder 40: 12)
    Typescript and correspondence with Guy Olson
  - "International Education," School Administrator, 1982 September? (Folder 40: 13)
    Typescript, printed copy, letter to Cindy Tursman, and related materials
  - "The University and America's Future," lecture, Cecil and Ida Green Distinguished Lecture Series, University of Texas at Dallas, Texas, 1982 September 21. (Folder 40: 14)
  - Article on "Special Report: Cost of Higher Education," Americana Annual/Encyclopedia Year Book, 1983. (Folder 40: 15)
    Typescript, galley, and letters from James E. Churchill, Jr.
  - "Education," World Book Year Book, World Book - Childcraft International, 1983. (Folder 40: 16)
    Galley and correspondence with Sara Dreyfuss
  - "Making Less Better," keynote speech, Dialogue for Change, sponsored by Saint Paul Community/School Collaborative and the Reflective Leadership Program, University of Minnesota, Humphrey Institute of Public Affairs, Minnesota, 1983 January 15. (Folder 40: 17)
    Typescript, correspondence, and related materials
  - Article on public schools, Institute for Educational Leadership, 1983 May 24. (Folder 40: 18)
    Galley, correspondence, and related materials
  - "New Trends in Educational Testing" (with Grace Hechinger), Reader's Digest, 1983 June? (Folder 40: 19)
    Galley and correspondence, including contract
  - Review of Diane Ravitch, The Troubled Crusade: American Education 1945-1980, The New Republic, 1983 September. (Folder 40: 20)
    Typescript, galley, and letter to Ann Hulbert
  - "Heroes, Villains and Wary Textbook Publishers," About Education, 1983 November 1. (Box-folder 41: 1)
    Typescript, printed copy, and correspondence with Don McKinney
  - Address, "Schools and Society: Confrontation or Accommodation," Tenth Annual Conference of Public and Non-Public Schools, City University of New York Graduate Center, New York City, New York, 1983 December 1. (Folder 41: 2)
  - "Education in America: Calls for Reform," Americana Annual/Encyclopedia Year Book, 1984? (Folder 41: 3)
    Galley and letter to James E., Churchill, Jr.
  - "What Works in Language Education," interview with Barry Kwalick, 1984 February 27. (Folder 41: 4)
    Typescript transcript and letter from Barry Kwalick
  - "Turnaround for the Public Schools?" Harvard Business Review, 1984 March. (Folder 41: 5)
    Galley, correspondence, including copyright agreement, and related materials
  - "School-College Collaboration: An Essential to Improved Public Education," remarks, Wingspread Conference on Integrating Computer Learning into the Curriculum and into the Community, sponsored by Educational Products Information Exchange (EPIE), International Council for Computers in Education (ICCE), Kentucky Educational Television (KET), and the Johnson Foundation, with assistance from the New York Times Foundation and the Markle Foundation, Racine, Wisconsin, 1984 March 27-28. (Folder 41: 6)
  - Remarks, Authors Guild Symposium, Textbook Selection Process, 1985 January 29. (Folder 41: 7)
    Typescript transcript, letters from Irwin Karp, printed copy, Authors Guild Bulletin, Spring 1985, and other materials
  - "Reading, Writing, and Electronics," Book Research Quarterly, 1985 Spring. (Folder 41: 8)
  - Article on curriculum reform, America Illustrated, United States Information Agency, 1985 July? (Folder 41: 9)
    Typescript and correspondence with Guy E. Olson and Gail Baker
  - Review of Harold L. Hodgkinson, All One System: Demographics of Education: Kindergarten Through Grade School, New York Times, 1985 August 13. (Folder 41: 10)
    Printed copy, letter from Michael D. Usdan, and related materials
  - "Report Card on Education," Ladies Home Journal, 1985 September. (Folder 41: 11)
  - Speech, the Silurians, New York, Player's Club, Gramercy Park, New York, 1985 October? (Folder 41: 12)
  - A Better Start: New Choices for Early Learning, ed., 1986
    - General (Folder 41: 13)
    - Correspondence (Folder 41: 14)
    - Printed copy (Folder 41: 15)
    - Reviews (Folder 41: 16)
  - Participant, discussion, "Measures on the College Admission Process," College Board Colloquium, Wakefield, Massachusetts, 1986 June. (Folder 41: 17)
    Typescript and letter from George H. Hanford
  - Article, Think, 1987 June. (Folder 41: 18)
    Typescript, galley, and letter to Woody Klein
  - "A Tribute" [to Alvin C. Eurich], Academy News, 1987 Fall. (Folder 41: 19)
  - Foreword to Diploma Mills, American Council on Education, 1988. (Folder 41: 20)
    Typescript and correspondence with Henry A. Spille
  - "The Major Concerns Facing Schools in 1988," Family Circle, 1988 April 29. (Folder 41: 21)
  - "Thirty-Eight Years on the Education Beat," interview with Deborah Walter, Scientists' Institute for Public Information (SIPI) Scope, 1988 Fall. (Folder 41: 22)
    Typescript transcript, printed copy, correspondence, and other materials
  - Foreword to "Excellence in English,", 1990? (Folder 41: 23)
- Newspaper Columns File, 1947-1990. (Box 42)
  Columns, correspondence, letters to the editor, permission requests, reviews and comments from readers relating to Fred Hechinger's columns in various newspapers, arranged alphabetically by name of newspaper and therein by physical form. Includes related materials
  - Unidentified (Folder 42: 1)
  - International Herald Tribune, 1979 (Folder 42: 2)
  - Middletown Daily Record, undated (Folder 42: 3)
  - New York Herald Tribune, 1956-1957.; See also Oversize File (Folder 42: 4)
  - New York Times, See also NEW YORK TIMES AND NEW YORK TIMES FOUNDATION FILE and Oversize File
    - Columns (some with Grace Hechinger)
      - Undated (Folder 42: 5-8)
      - Undated (Box-folder 43: 1)
      - 1959-1969 (Folder 43: 2)
      - 1970-1978 (Folder 43: 3)
      - 1979-1990 (Folder 43: 4)
    - Correspondence (Box 44)
      - Undated (Folder 44: 1)
      - 1950-1979 (Folder 44: 2)
      - 1980 (Folder 44: 3)
      - 1981 (Folder 44: 4)
      - 1982-1983 (Folder 44: 5)
      - 1984-1985 (Box-folder 45: 1)
      - 1986 (Folder 45: 2)
      - 1987-1990 (Folder 45: 3)
    - Letters to the editor from readers.
      Includes columns by others
      - Undated (Folder 45: 4)
      - 1976-1985 (Folder 45: 5)
      - 1986-1990 (Folder 45: 6)
    - Permission requests, 1961-1989. (Folder 45: 7)
      Includes some columns
    - Reviews and comments from readers (Box 46)
      - Undated (Folder 46: 1)
      - 1960-1976 (Folder 46: 2)
      - 1977-1978 (Folder 46: 3)
      - 1979
        - January-February (Folder 46: 4)
        - March (Folder 46: 5)
        - April (Folder 46: 6)
        - May-September (Box-folder 47: 1)
        - October-December (Folder 47: 2)
      - 1980
        - January-July (Folder 47: 3)
        - August-December (Folder 47: 4)
      - 1981
        - January-May (Folder 47: 5)
        - June-July (Folder 47: 6)
        - August-September (Folder 47: 7)
        - October-December (Folder 47: 8)
      - 1982 (Box 48)
        - January-March (Folder 48: 1)
        - April-June (Folder 48: 2)
        - July-September (Folder 48: 3)
        - October (Folder 48: 4)
        - November-December (Folder 48: 5)
      - 1983
        - January-February (Folder 48: 6)
        - March-April (Folder 48: 7)
        - May (Box-folder 49: 1)
        - June-July (Folder 49: 2)
        - August (Folder 49: 3)
        - September (Folder 49: 4)
        - October (Folder 49: 5)
        - November-December (Folder 49: 6)
      - 1984
        - January (Folder 49: 7)
        - February-March (Folder 49: 8)
        - April-June (Box-folder 50: 1)
        - July-October (Folder 50: 2)
        - November-December (Folder 50: 3)
      - 1985
        - January-February (Folder 50: 4)
        - March-April (Folder 50: 5)
        - May-June (Folder 50: 6)
        - July-October (Folder 50: 7)
        - November-December (Folder 50: 8)
      - 1986 (Box 51)
        - January-February (Folder 51: 1)
        - March-April (Folder 51: 2)
        - May-June (Folder 51: 3)
        - July-August (Folder 51: 4)
        - September-October (Folder 51: 5)
        - November-December (Folder 51: 6)
      - 1987
        - January-February (Folder 51: 7)
        - March-April (Folder 51: 8)
        - May-July (Box-folder 52: 1)
        - August-October (Folder 52: 2)
        - November-December (Folder 52: 3)
      - 1988
        - January-February (Folder 52: 4)
        - March-April (Folder 52: 5)
        - May-August (Folder 52: 6)
        - September-December (Folder 52: 7)
      - 1989 (Box 53)
        - January-March (Folder 53: 1)
        - April-May (Folder 53: 2)
        - August-December (Folder 53: 3)
      - 1990 January-December (Folder 53: 4)
  - Santa Barbara News Press, 1981 (Folder 53: 5)
  - Sunday Herald., See also Oversize File
    - Columns
      - Undated (Folder 53: 6)
      - 1947/1958 (Folder 53: 7)
    - Correspondence, 1947-1965 (Folder 53: 8)
  - York Gazette. Column, 1948 (Folder 53: 9)
- New York Times and New York Times Foundation File, 1958-1989.; See also Oversize File.
  Announcements, congratulatory messages, correspondence, memoranda, printed matter, purchase requisitions, reports, travel orders, and miscellany relating to Fred Hechinger's long association with the New York Times and with the New York Times Foundation, arranged alphabetically by physical form and therein chronologically.
  - Announcements of Fred Hechinger's appointments as managing editor of the New York Times and president of the New York Times Foundation. (Folder 53: 10)
    Includes a note of introduction for Fred Hechinger
  - Congratulatory messages
    - Undated (Folder 53: 11)
    - 1969 (Folder 53: 12)
    - 1976 (Folder 53: 13)
    - 1977-1990 (Box-folder 54: 1)
  - Correspondence
    - Undated (Folder 54: 2)
    - 1959 – 1976 April (Folder 54: 3)
    - 1976 May-December (Folder 54: 4)
    - 1977 (Folder 54: 5)
    - 1978 (Box-folder 55: 1)
    - 1979 (Folder 55: 2)
    - 1980 (Folder 55: 3)
    - 1981 (Folder 55: 4)
    - 1982 (Folder 55: 5)
    - 1983
      - January-May (Folder 56: 1)
      - June-October (Folder 56: 2)
      - November-December (Folder 56: 3)
    - 1984
      - January-March (Folder 56: 4)
      - April-May (Folder 56: 5)
      - June-October (Box-folder 57: 1)
      - November-December (Folder 57: 2)
    - 1985
      - January-April (Folder 57: 3)
      - May-September (Folder 57: 4)
      - October-November 15 (Box-folder 58: 1)
      - November 19-December (Folder 58: 2)
    - 1986
      - January-February (Folder 59: 1)
      - March-April (Folder 59: 2)
      - May (Folder 59: 3)
      - June (Box-folder 60: 1)
      - July-August (Folder 60: 2)
      - September-October (Box-folder 61: 1)
      - November-December (Folder 61: 2)
    - 1987
      - January (Folder 61: 3)
      - February (Folder 61: 4)
      - March-April (Box-folder 62: 1)
      - May (Folder 62: 2)
      - June-August (Folder 62: 3)
      - September-October (Box-folder 63: 1)
      - November-December 8 (Folder 63: 2)
      - December 10-22 (Folder 63: 3)
    - 1988
      - January-March 15 (Folder 64: 1)
      - March 18-April (Folder 64: 2)
      - May (Folder 64: 3)
      - June-July (Box-folder 65: 1)
      - August (Folder 65: 2)
      - September-December (Folder 65: 3)
    - 1989
      - January-February (Folder 66: 1)
      - March-April (Folder 66: 2)
      - May-December (Folder 66: 3)
    - 1990-1991 (Folder 66: 4)
  - Memoranda. (Box 67)
    - Undated (Folder 67: 1)
    - 1959-1976 (Folder 67: 2)
    - 1977 (Folder 67: 3)
    - 1978 (Folder 67: 4)
    - 1979 (Folder 67: 5)
    - 1980 (Folder 67: 6)
    - 1981 (Box-folder 68: 1)
    - 1982 (Folder 68: 2)
    - 1983 (Folder 68: 3)
    - 1984 (Folder 68: 4)
    - 1985 (Folder 68: 5)
    - 1986
      - January-April (Folder 68: 6)
      - June-December (Box-folder 69: 1)
    - 1987 (Folder 69: 2)
    - 1988 (Folder 69: 3)
    - 1989-1990 (Folder 69: 4)
  - Printed matter (Folder 69: 5)
  - Purchase requisitions (Folder 69: 6)
  - Reports of the New York Times Foundation, 1978 and 1988, by Fred Hechinger (Folder 69: 7)